export const data = [
    {
        question: "The piece of hardware that converts you computer’s digital signal to an analog signal that can travel over telephone lines is called a ?",
        option1: "red wire ",
        option2: "blue cord",
        option3: "tower",
        option4: "modem ",
        ans: 4
    },
    {
        question: "	In a web site, the ‘home’ page refers to ?",
        option1: "the best page ",
        option2: "the last page",
        option3: "the first page",
        option4: "the most recent page",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "	A ________ is a software program used to view Web pages ?",
        option1: "site ",
        option2: "host",
        option3: "link",
        option4: "browser",
        ans: 4
    },
    {
        question: "	Sending an E-mail is similar to ?",
        option1: "writing a letter ",
        option2: "drawing a picture",
        option3: "talking on the phone",
        option4: "sending a package ",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "A program, either talk or music, that is made available in digital format tor automatic download over the Internet is called a __________ ?",
        option1: "wiki",
        option2: "broadcast",
        option3: "vodcast ",
        option4: "podcast",
        ans: 4
    },
    {
        question: "A (n) ________ appearing on a web page opens another document when clicked ?",
        option1: "anchor",
        option2: "URL ",
        option3: "hyperlink",
        option4: "reference ",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Digital Banking can be resorted through ?",
        option1: "Mobile phones ",
        option2: "Internet ",
        option3: "Telephones ",
        option4: "All of these",
        ans: 4
    },
    {
        question: "A chat is ?",
        option1: "an internet standard that allows users to upload and download files ",
        option2: "a typed conversation that takes place on a computer ",
        option3: "an online area in which users conduct written discussions about a particular subject ",
        option4: "the transmission of messages and files via a computer network ",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "While sending an e-mail, the –– line describes the contents of the message ?",
        option1: "subject",
        option2: "to",
        option3: "contents ",
        option4: "cc ",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "The _____enables you to simultaneously keep multiple Web pages open in one browser window ?",
        option1: "tab box ",
        option2: "pop-up helper",
        option3: "tab row",
        option4: "address bar ",
        ans: 3
    },
]